Finding aid for the Experiments in Art and Technology records, 1966-1993 (bulk 1966-1973)
Experiments in Art and Technology records
- Correspondence and administration, 1966-1980; Series II.; 21 lin. ft. 16 boxes
  - Correspondence, 1966-1974 (Box 122)
    - Francis Mason (President of E.A.T.), 1968 (Box 122, Folder 29-39)
      with artists, industry, universities, museums, arts organizations and government officials, primarily about fund-raising, collaborations and organization. Includes a letter from Carol Brown expressing disappointment in E.A.T.'s lack of assistance with her projects; 3 p. letter from Ross Drago about his work and E.A.T. Bay Area local group formation with 4 photos; 2 letters from Dan Flavin requesting assistance; note from Buckminster Fuller agreeing to join the board; 4 items with Douglas Davis, National Observer, who eagerly wants to write about E.A.T. and related developments in art and technology (see also Box 125); 1 p. cc. of a typescript from Max Newhaus describing the development of his electronic music; and letter from Paik discussing a new "art machine"; ca. .25 lin. ft., filed in rough alpha order.
  - Correspondence, 1967-1980 (Box 123)
    - General, 1967-1980, 1968-1972 (Box 123, Folder 1-28)
      with various E.A.T. staff members and interested persons similar to those mentioned above in Klüver and Mason correspondence, concerning a myriad of topics, filed in chron. order. 1969-1970 files contain mostly carbon copies and photocopies of letters, and drafts of letters, memos and financial reports (some duplicating those in Klüver and Mason correspondence and in Project files). 1970-1972 has much on financial matters, showing an increased difficulty with paying bills. From 1971 until 1980 a substantial proportion of the letters ask and answer queries. Some highlights are: 2 letters from Udo Kasemets about Klüver giving a lecture at a festival in Canada (Dec 22 1967, Feb 24 1968); apologetic note from Robert Venturi (Apr 2 1968); Galeria Bonino press release for Paik's "Electronic Art II" (ca. Apr 1968); 3 notes from Gyorgy Kepes (Sep 23 1968, May 12 1969, Jun 12 1969); letter from Alison Knowles about creating houses on a plot of ground in Chelsea (Nov 22 1968, see Jan 1969); typescript of 16 p. Klüver paper which describes in detail Tinguely's "Hommage à New York" among other things (Jan 27 1969); proposal for 10 exhibitions at Automation House (Mar 17 1969); Jud Yalkut proposal (May 1 1969); postcard from Geoff Hendricks (Jun 1969); much pertaining to the Pavilion (Apr-Jul 1969); correspondence between Martin, Nakaya and Mrs. Naum Gabo about printing and casting some of Gabo's work (Apr 1969, Sep 9 1969); postcard from Richard Kostelanetz (Aug 1 1969); letter from Schneemann requesting sponsor list (Aug 5 1970); letter from Brian O'Doherty who will not recommend E.A.T.'s membership-publications program grant proposal because his own organization (NEA) has turned it down (Mar 22 1971); note from Joseph Kosuth (ca. 1973); 3 letters from Peter Frank requesting information for an exhibition with response from Klüver (1973); note from Allan Kaprow (1973); chatty letter and a postcard from Jackie Monnier (Sep 29 1980); and letter from Terry Martin with family photograph taken ca. 1907 (Apr 1 1980).
  - Correspondence and General Files A-BR, 1968, 1981-1993 (Box 124)
    - General correspondence, 1981-1993 (Box 124, Folder 1-11)
      Includes photocopy of a letter from Nakaya about copyrighting her fog sculptures with a thick packet of material on her work (Aug 15 1981); postcard from Germano Celant (ca. 1982); letters with the Cooper Union about borrowing Rauschenberg's tennis racket used in "Open Score" (1983); and two letters from Matthew Rinaldo, House of Representatives, concerning NEA grant policies and censorship (1990); ca. .33 lin. ft.
    - General files, A-BR, 1968 (Box 124, Folder 12-37)
      contains much correspondence, publications and clippings concerning a variety of topics. Includes: Amer. Ass. for the Advancement of Science correspondence and transcript of Klüver's talk at their annual meeting (1968); ephemera relating to artists exhibitions; and Automation House files containing job training film festival material (1968), reports, memos, pamphlets and clippings about Theodore Kheel.
  - General Files BU-INS, 1968-1977, 1970-1973 (Box 125, Folder 1-50)
    Including correspondence and press releases with Frank Stanton, CBS, regarding the House of Reps. subpeona of various materials relating to CBS's broadcast "The Selling of the Pentagon"; correspondence with Lowell Cross (ca. 8 items); Douglas Davis correspondence regarding his book "Art and the Future," ca. 15 items (1969-1972); E.A.T. history notes with a letter from Waldhauer describing the sentiments of some of the board members (Summer 1971); 13 articles by Robert Feller (conservator); and IEEE correspondence about creating an IEEE group concentrating on art.
  - General Files INT-O, 1968-1977, 1970-1973 (Box 126, Folder 1-55)
    Including typescript of Deane Judd's 28 p. paper "Visual Science and the Artist"; King's Square Show (Barbara Rose project) financial correspondence and organizational material; Mabou Mines (theater group) file with a note from Philip Glass (1973), project proposal, ephemera and photocopied reviews; some Robert McFarland correspondence regarding fund-raising (1969-1970); 6 issues of "Marijuana"; and postcard signed by Charlotte Moorman and Paik (1974).
  - General Files P-Z, 1968-1977, 1970-1973 (Box 127, Folder 1-52)
    Including photocopied publications, rules and contracts relating to Public Access TV; many photocopied articles and other material concerning Pulsa (seven-man team of research associates at Yale); substantial quantity of resumes; articles and catalogs regarding Super 8; questionnaires and other material relating to "Toward the year 2018" a convocation sponsored by the Foreign Policy Association; and much material about Westbeth artists' housing with note from Carl Andre written on a Westbeth letter he received.
  - Board of Directors, 1966-1974 (Box 128, Folder 1-58)
    Includes material on board formation and activities, but mostly meeting minutes and notes from and agendas for board, advisory council and executive committee meetings, 1 lin. ft.
  - Administrative Activities, ca. 1966-1983 (Box 129)
    - E.A.T. Formation, ca. 1966-ca. 1980s (Box 129, Folder 1-6)
      by-laws, certificate of incorporation, certificate of charitable organization, philosophy notes and statements, and statement of purpose.
    - Office Management, 1971-1983 (Box 129, Folder 7-34)
      includes staff bios; stenograph notebooks (early 70s); phone call numbers and lists (1971-1983); desk calendars (1971-1972); equipment orders, agreements and catalogs; letterhead typesetting and printing (1969-1980); and mailing procedures and information; ca. .75 lin. ft.
  - Miscellaneous Administrative Activities, 1969 (Box 130, Folder 1-11)
    Includes interoffice memos, internal correspondence, meeting notes, office procedures, and office reorganization material.
  - Fund-raising, 1966-1972, 1967-1969 (Box 131)
    - Tamblyn & Brown Fund-raising Feasibility Study, 1967 (Box 131, Folder 1-5)
      correspondence with Tamblyn & Brown, form letter sent requesting industry to participate, checklists of contacts, questionnaires and mailers, and report.
    - Fund-raising correspondence (Box 131, Folder 6-9)
      substantial quantity of carbon copies and photocopies of letters from various E.A.T. staff/ board members to potential donors/sponsors with some responses.
    - Notes (Box 131, Folder 10-12)
      on donor prospects and corporate contacts.
    - Donations, 1966-1969 (Box 131, Folder 13-17)
      includes lists of donors, and records of donations and deposits to E.A.T.
    - Donor Files, A (Box 131, Folder 18-30)
      mostly correspondence and some grant application material with organizations such as AFL-CIO and Robert Anderson (ARCO). Oftentimes files were annotated with donation amount, ca. .25 lin. ft. (cont.).
  - Fund-raising, 1966-1972, 1967-1969 (Box 132)
    - Donor files, B-N (Box 132, Folder 1-44)
      same as above and includes CBS, IBM, NEA grant application, New York State Council on the Arts, and Rockefeller Brothers Fund.
  - Klüver notes, ca. 1967-1972 (Box 133)
    - Klüver calendar, and photograph of Klüver and Rauschenberg, 1968 ca. 1967-1972 (Box 133, Folder 1-2)
    - Notes, 1967-1972 (Folder 3-18)
      pertain to various E.A.T. projects, ideas, contacts, with drafts of letters and memos, ca. 1 lin. ft.
  - Klüver notes, early 1970s (Box 134)
    - Bound notebooks and memopads recording ideas and daily activities (Box 134, Folder 1-4)
    - Klüver research files (Box 134, Folder 5-13)
      continuation of notes but with a greater abundance of clippings, publications, and invitations.
  - Julie Martin's notes, undated (Box 135)
    - Notes, drafts, assorted clippings and photocopied articles (Box 135, Folder 1-27)
  - Rolodex and other card files, 1970s (Box 136-137)
    Three sets of rolodex card files; small group of index cards with names and addresses (corporate sponsors?); and inventory cards (ca. 1978) with artists' names, title of work, date, price and other pertinent information
- Publications, ca. 1967-1980; Series III.; ca. 15 lin. ft. 10 boxes, 1 flat file folder
  Contains book and newsletter production material in the form of manuscripts, galleys, proofs and layouts for most of E.A.T.'s publications, arranged in rough chronological order. Invoices, order forms and letters of interest record E.A.T.'s marketing and subscribing membership activities
  - Publications, 1967-1970 (Box 138)
    - Art and Technology, ca. 1967-1968 (Box 138, Folder 1-4)
      notes, ms, galley, article copy, title. search.
    - E.A.T. News, vol.1, nos.1-4,; vol.2, nos.1-2, 1967 1968 (Box 138, Folder 5-12)
      mss., reports, information, newsletter copies.
    - E.A.T. Operations and Information, nos.1-5, 1968-1969 (Box 138, Folder 13-17)
      journal copies and some manuscript material.
    - E.A.T. Information, Sep 1969, Feb 1970, Mar 1970 (Box 138, Folder 18-21)
      mss. and journal copies (see also Box 44 for more mss.).
    - President's Report, Oct 1969 (Box 138, Folder 22)
      mss. and journal copy.
    - E.A.T. Proceedings, 1967-1969 (Box 138, Folder 23-29)
      Numbers 1, 4-5, 9, 11-13. Journal copies, mailing list, safety report, bibliography, covers.
    - Techne, vol.1, no.1, Apr 1969 (Box 138, Folder 31-36)
      journal;, ideas, notes, mss (includes Carl Andre letter), photos, correspondence.
    - Techne, vol.1, no.2, Nov 1970 (Box 138, Folder 37-70)
      journal, mss (some not included in final printing), paste-up (see also Box 106), repros, illus., graphics, copyright certificate, ad material, ca. .5 lin. ft.
  - Publications, 1969-1972, undated (Box 139)
    - Techne, vol.1, no.2, Nov 1970 (Box 139, Folder 1-2)
    - Techne, vol.1, no.3 (unpublished) (Box 139, Folder 3)
      Notes and correspondence requesting article submissions.
    - Techne, vol.1, no.3 (unpublished) (Box 139, Folder 4-6)
      Deane Judd interview transcript.
    - Automation House ( New York Times Supplement), 1969 (Box 139, Folder 11-17)
      meeting minutes, correspondence, memos, notes, ms, cover dummy, dummy.
    - Pavilion, 1972 (Box 139, Folder 18-40)
      Dutton contract, correspondence, substantial quantity of mss. many with corrections and mostly of Nilo Lindgren's section. Also contains 2 versions of Barbara Rose's manuscript, ca. .75 lin. ft.
  - Publications, 1968-1970 (Box 140)
    - Pavilion, 1968-1970 (Box 140, Folder 1-25)
      ms. corrections, interview transcripts and appointment lists for interviews, galleys, proofs, permission requests,illus. lists and captions, illus., promotion.
    - Description of the Pepsi-Cola Pavilion (Box 140, Folder 27)
      Breer notes, ms, galley, booklet.
  - Publications, 1967-1974 (Box 141)
    - E.A.T. Brochure (Box 141, Folder 1-10)
      drafts (1967-1969), collection of writings by E.A.T., mss, paste-ups, notes, dummies, schematic layout, captions, information on printing, and "Brochure for Industry" mss. [See also art work for E.A.T. brochure, in flat file folder 8**.]
    - Subscribing members (Box 141, Folder 12-32)
      includes membership request letters and forms (1968-1974), potentials (1970-1973), letters to members (1968-1971), letter to members (Oct 2, 1970, not mailed), subscribing members list (ca. 1970), membership mailer (ca. 1970), and membership circular manuscript, outline, notes and layout examples.
  - Publications, 1967-1986 (Box 142)
    - Printing (Box 142, Folder 1-12)
      includes jobs (1967-1970), publications worksheets, receipts, expense log.
    - Marketing (Box 142, Folder 13-27)
      order form, orders and invoices (1970, 1977-1979, 1983-1986), inventory (1971), catalogs and price lists (ca. 1972), price list (1980), catalog layout (ca. 1980), trademark and copyright information, mailing lists.
    - Miscellaneous (Box 142, Folder 28-44)
      includes book ideas and suggestions, procedures, press releases, clippings, to-do lists, ISBN information
  - E.A.T. Bibliography, 1965-1980 (Box 143, Folder 1-36)
    Early drafts (1974, 1978); notebook for indexing references; citation drafts; notes (includes all vols. of E.A.T. News bound in one volume); mss.; many photocopied page proofs; paste-ups; corrections; dummies; layouts.
  - E.A.T. Bibliography, 1965-1980 (Box 144, Folder 1-23)
    Bound signatures; bound signatures w/cover; cover design; cover; NEA grant application; E.A.T. Documents notes, correspondence and packaging; sales and marketing; notes.
  - E.A.T. Bibliography, 1965-1980 (Box 145, Folder 1-13)
    Original material published or produced by E.A.T. used to compile archive box documents sent to libraries and for book, 1965-1969, #1-151.
  - E.A.T. Bibliography, 1965-1980 (Box 146, Folder 1-14)
    Similar material to Box 145, 1970-Oct 1971, #151A-251.
  - E.A.T. Bibliography, 1965-1980 (Box 147, Folder 1-15)
    Similar material to Box 145, Nov 1971-1993, #252-361.
  - Artwork for E.A.T. brochure (Oversize 8**)
- Clippings, 1965-ca. 1980; Series IV.; 8 lin. ft. 16 boxes
  Contains over 600 citations of articles, notices and press accounts, filed chronologically. In many cases the full magazine, newspaper or other publication where the article appears has been included. The citations for these press clippings is contained within the publication, E.A.T. Bibliography 1965-1980. Some material has been added since 1980.
  - 1965-Jun 1967 (Box 148)
  - Jul 1967-Oct 1968 (Box 149)
  - Nov 1968-Feb 1969 (Box 150)
  - Mar 1969-Sep 1969 (Box 151)
  - Oct 1969-Jan 1970 (Box 152)
  - and Expo '70 guides, Jan 1970-Mar 1970 (Box 153)
  - Apr 1970-Jun 1970 (Box 154)
  - Jul-Dec 1970 (Box 155)
  - Pavilion and Bijutsu-Techo, 1970, Jan 1971-Sep 1971 (Box 156)
  - Bijutsu-Techo, Oct 1971-Dec 1971, 1971 (Box 157)
  - Jan 1972-Sep 1973 (Box 158)
  - Oct 1973-Jan 1974 (Box 159)
  - J.D.Rockefeller III Report ( ), Feb 1974-1978, 1977 (Box 160)
  - 1979 (Box 161)
  - 1980-1981, 1983, 1991 (Box 162)
  - Oversize, 1966, 1968-1971 (Box 163)
    "9 Evenings: Theatre and Engineering" program (Oct 1966), Techne (Apr 14, 1969 and Nov 6, 1970), Projects Outside Art poster (Jun 12, 1970), "Utopier et Visioner" Moderna Museet Stockholm (1971), "Some More Beginnings" catalog (1968), "E.A.T. Clippings" (Apr 1960-Jul 1969).
- Financial, 1966-1986, 1966-1974; Series V.; ca. 25.5 lin. ft. 17 boxes
  Includes bank-account statements, cancelled checks, check stubs, ledgers, project budgets, bills, receipts, disbursements, and tax and IRS forms. Throughout the early 1970s, E.A.T. tended to operate with its finances in arrears. Financial strains first began to show during the construction of the Pepsi Pavilion. By 1973-1974, most bills were either paid late or went into collection. Correspondence on these matters is interspersed.
  - "9 Evenings,", 1963-1966 (Box 164)
    - Bank records, 1966 (Box 164, Folder 1-11)
      Stockholm Festival account statements (Summit & Elisabeth Trust Co.) deposit slips and cancelled checks for 9 Evenings account (Bankers Trust Co.) includes bills paid on account, deposits and check stubs; Klüver personal account (Summit & Elisabeth Trust Co.); cancelled checks and receipts E.A.T. account (c/o Rauschenberg, Chemical Bank NY) statements Oct 12, 1966.
    - Accounting records, 1963-1965 (Box 164, Folder 12-56)
      budget, ledger and purchase books, individual files for expense reports of "9 Evenings" artists, electric and lighting bills, receipts for unpaid bills, expense and donation summary, Rubin Gorewitz CPA correspondence and receipt files (see also Box 4 for accounting ledger1963-1965, payroll and box office accounting).
  - 1967-1969 (Box 165)
    - Bank statements, cancelled checks, some deposit slips (Box 165, Folder 1-14)
  - 1966-1970, 1968-1969 (Box 166)
    - Deposit slips, advice, 1967-1969 (Box 166, Folder 1-6)
    - Check stubs, Nov 1966-Aug 1970 (Box 166, Folder 7-20)
    - Staff tax accounts, checkbook, 1969 (Box 166, Folder 21)
    - Petty cash account, 1969 (Box 166, Folder 22-26)
      statements and cancelled checks (Jan-Dec), receipts, and check stubs (Nov-Dec).
  - 1966-1970, 1968-1969 (Box 167, Folder 1-39)
    Bills/invoices (1967), paid bills A-Z (1968), and bills and receipts A-Z (1969-1970), .66 lin. ft.
  - 1966-1970, 1968-1969 (Box 168)
    - E.A.T. budgets, 1966-1970 (Box 168, Folder 1)
    - Gorewitz correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 168, Folder 2)
    - Ordover correspondence, 1967-1970 (Box 168, Folder 3)
    - Accounting, 1966-1967 (Box 168, Folder 4-8)
      Gorewitz year-end reports, liabilities, budgets and expenditures, report on activities.
    - Accounting, 1968 (Box 168, Folder 9-16)
      bookkeeping procedures, contributions, Mason expense report, bank reconciliation work papers, ledgers, cash disbursement ledgers, Gorewitz year-end report, and miscellaneous.
    - Accounting, 1969 (Box 168, Folder 17-36)
      budgets/ledgers, assets and liabilities, operating expenses, bookkeeping / salary, payroll and personnel, bank overdraft correspondence, tax exemption certificate, insurance, general ledger, forecast, year-end report, and report on activities. See also Box 50 for general financial ledger, 1969.
  - Pepsi Pavilion, 1969-1970 (Box 169)
    - Budget-cost management (Box 169, Folder 1-27)
      cost reviews and estimates, mirror dome and fog costs/specs, equipment prices/price changes, Schjeldahl contract, Singer correspondence, allocation of overhead expenses, cost/budget analysis, film proposal/est. budget, TIE budgets, budget adjustments and forecasts, and estimated/actual budgets.
    - Accounting (Box 169, Folder 28-63)
      petty cash account receipts, receipted bills A-Z and expense log, shipping, and materials invoices and costs.
  - Pepsi Pavilion, 1969-1970 (Box 170)
    - Accounting (Box 170, Folder 1-18)
      accounts payable/receivable, ledgers, overhead account 1022 analysis, disbursements, and Pepsi reports and correspondence.
    - Travel expenses (Box 170, Folder 19-54)
      expense reports and receipts filed alpha by traveler, including Robert Breer, Karl Friberg, Toshi Ichiyanagi, Klüver, Julie Martin, Forrest Myers, Fujiko Nakaya, Larry Owens, John Pearce, John Ryde, David Tudor, Fred Waldhauer and Robert Whitman; PepsiCo advances; and charter flight final payments.
  - Pepsi Pavilion, 1969-1970 (Box 171)
    - Personnel (Box 171, Folder 1-8)
      procedures, E.A.T.-IRS correspondence about payroll taxes, payroll tax ledgers and forms/worksheets, salary/benefits, and responsibilities for Pavilion.
    - Nakaya file on Expo '70 operations (Box 171, Folder 9)
    - Press (Box 171, Folder 10-14)
      activities, budgets, and costs.
    - E.A.T. LA [Los Angeles] (Box 171, Folder 15-38)
      includes California qualification forms, account statements and cancelled checks, paid bills, accounts payable, budget, amounts owed/paid, general ledger, monthly reports/disbursements, dome cost estimates, staff tax account and payroll.
    - Settlement (Box 171, Folder 39-40)
      agreement, Pepsi correspondence, and letters to creditors.
  - 1970-1971 (Box 172)
    - Bank statements and cancelled checks (Box 172, Folder 1-24)
      Chemical Bank (Jan-Aug 1970) with check stubs (Feb-Jul 1970), staff tax acct. (Jan-Aug 1970), Manufacturers Hanover (Jul-Dec 1970) with check stubs (Aug-Oct 1970), petty cash account and receipts (1970), account statements and cancelled checks (Jan 1971-Jan 1972).
    - Accounting (Box 172, Folder 25-27)
      general ledger (1970, 1971) and payroll ledger (1971, 1972). See also Box 106 for more ledgers.
  - 1970 (Box 173)
    - Accounting (Box 173, Folder 1-38)
      includes bills, A-Z, disbursements (Jun-Dec), deposit breakdown (Sep-Dec), accounts payable, payment schedule, trial balance, moneys owed, accounting summaries for Artists in India, Projects Outside Art, and Wash. D.C. visit. Also financial statements and journal entries.
  - Accounting, 1970-1972, 1971-1972 (Box 174, Folder 1-43)
    bills, A-Z (1970-1972), bills outstanding (1971), disbursements (Jan-Dec 1971), and accounts receivable (1970-1971).
  - 1970-1971 (Box 175)
    - Accounting (Box 175, Folder 1-13)
      includes projected budget (1971), accounts payable, journal entries and CPA worksheets, report worksheets (1971);, and controller (J.A. Ruffalo) correspondence.
    - Taxes, 1966-1971 (Box 175, Folder 14-39)
      includes forms, exemption letter (1969), annual report of charitable organization (1966-1971, all filed 1970-1971), returns (1966-1970), W-2 and W-4 forms, quarterly withholdings and disability, papers marked "Hold for Audit" (1970), withholding tax penalties (1971), payroll taxes (1971) and balance sheet (1971).
    - Personnel, 1970-1971 (Box 175, Folder 40-60)
      completed time sheets (1970), terminated employees (1970), vacation schedules (1970), N.Y. State Employment information, unemployment and disability, resumes, and personal and Klüver expenses (1971).
  - 1968-1974, 1970-1971 (Box 176)
    - Insurance (Box 176, Folder 1-6)
      policies, group insurance registration cards, and information
    - Fund-raising, 1968-1971 (Box 176, Folder 7-15)
      statement of potential (1968), grants in progress including JDR II and Ford Foundation (1970), Klüver donation (1971), and loans (1971).
    - Leasing, 1969-1972 (Box 176, Folder 16-24)
      office space, and equipment and furniture.
    - Legal (Box 176, Folder 25-29)
      De Forest and Duer corresp (1970), Julie Martin files (1971-1974), and copyright information.
  - 1972-1973 (Box 177)
    - Accounting, 1972-1973 (Box 177, Folder 1-30)
      bills owed/paid (1972), accountant file (1972), disbursements (Jan 1972-Dec 1973), disbursement ledger (1973), and deposit slips/breakdown (1973).
    - Taxes, 1972 (Box 177, Folder 31-38)
      returns and withholdings.
    - Insurance policies (Box 177, Folder 39-40)
    - Fund-raising, 1973 (Box 177, Folder 41)
      grant applications.
  - 1972-1975, 1973-1974 (Box 178)
    - Banking (Box 178, Folder 1-15)
      statements and cancelled checks (1972-1974), deposit slips (Jan-Jun 1974, Manufacturers Hanover), statements and cancelled checks (Oct-Nov, 1974, United Counties Trust account), statements, cancelled checks and overdraft notices from loan account (1972-1975), check stubs (1973-1974), and stop payments and returned checks (1973).
    - Accounting (Box 178, Folder 16-18)
      petty cash receipts (1973), lawsuits and creditor claims (1973), and collected moneys for Stockholm trip (1973).
    - Taxes and IRS (Box 178, Folder 19-21)
      NY State taxes 1972, NY Employee taxes 1974, and IRS 1973.
    - Miscellaneous (Box 178, Folder 22-27)